goandroid.co.in 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy - GoAndroid

**What information do we collect?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We use Ezoic services for advertising purposes, you can check their [privacy policy over here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/goandroid.co.in).

 **GDPR compliance for European region**

In compliance with European privacy laws, in particular the European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Android Authority provides specific additional rights for citizens of the European Territories such as the right to access, rectification, right to object, to complaint, erasure outband blockage. More specifically:

  * The right to request information about whether and which personal data is processed by us, and the right to demand that personal data is rectified or amended.
  * Under certain circumstances, the right to request that personal data should be deleted.
  * Under certain circumstances, the right to demand that the processing of personal data should be restricted.
  * Withdraw your consent to the processing and use of your data completely or partially at any time with future application.
  * Have the right to obtain your personal data in a common, structured and mechanically readable format.
  * Contact our data protection officer if there are any questions, comments, complaints or requests in connection with our statement on data protection and the processing of your personal data.
  * The right to complain to the responsible supervisory authority if believed that the processing of your personal data is in violation of the legislation.

In addition to the above, we reference certain rights for European Territory citizens throughout this Privacy Policy. Pursuant to the GDPR, citizens from “European Territories” mean the European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, the term “European Territories” shall continue to include the United Kingdom, even after the United Kingdom leaves the European Economic Area following Brexit.

Please email admin[at]goandroid[dot]co[dot]in with the subject line “GDPR Request” for any questions about exercising any of the above rights.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at .

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.goandroid.co.in
